A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), Laurance S. Rockefeller General Files, 1992-1996, RG 43 FA1325
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1992-1996; 36
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Pesticide, 1992-1996 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Rockwood Hall, 1992-1996 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Sale to NAR Jr., Mark Rockefeller, 1992-1996 (Box 80, Folder 8-12)
  - Property - Pocantico Hills - Sale to Eugene R. Giarratana, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Property - Teton Ranch Company, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 2-4)
  - Property - Woodstock - General, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Property - Woodstock - Frye (Box 81, Folder 6-7)
  - Property - Woodstock - A - Z (Box 81, Folder 8-10)
  - Property - Woodstock - LSR Properties and Account Balances, 1988-1993 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Property - Woodstock - Articles, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Property - Woodstock - Articles - Town and Country, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Property - Woodstock - Bailey House, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - General, 1993-1995 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Property - Woodstock - Billings Farm - Budget, 1989-1991 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Property - Woodstock - Marsh Billings National Historic Park, 1989-1991 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Property - Woodstock - Carriages, 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Property - Woodstock - Cash Disbursements, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Property - Woodstock - Debevoise, Thomas M., 1992-1996 (Box 81, Folder 21-22)
  - Property - Woodstock - Debevoise, Thomas M. (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
  - Property - Woodstock - Echo Acre, 1992-1996 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Property - Woodstock - LSR Properties, Account and Budgets, 1992-1994 (Box 82, Folder 4-5)
  - Property - Woodstock - Finances (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Property - Woodstock - Finances - Cash Requirements, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Property - Woodstock - Mansion, 1992-1996 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Property - Woodstock - Suicide Six, 1992-1996 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Property - Woodstock - "Three Women of Woodstock: Inheritors of a Vision" Book, 1992-1996 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 83, Folder 1-4)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 83, Folder 6-12)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 84, Folder 1-7)
  - Property - Woodstock - USG - Department of Interior - National Park Service - Marsh Billings National Historical Park, 1992-1996 (Box 85, Folder 1-16)
  - Property - Woodstock - Winks, Robin, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1986 October 21 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Frye, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Pomeroy, 1986-1993 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Frye - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Balance Sheet and Financials, 1992-1994 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum, 1992-1994 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Attendance, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Tenth Anniversary, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - General, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 14-15)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Board of Trustees, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Billings Farm and Museum - Contributions, 1992-1996 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film - Billington, Dr. James H., 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film - Crawford, Frederick C., 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Property - Woodstock - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film - Hecksher, August, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film - James Madison Council of the Library of Congress, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation - Calvin Coolidge Film - Trip to Morven Farms, Charlottesville, 1992 April (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Finances, 1992-1996 (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Financials, 1994-1995 (Box 87, Folder 12-13)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Finances Rock and Co. Statements, 1992-1994 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - General Correspondence, 1994 (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
  - Property - Woodstock - Woodstock Foundation - LSR Convservation Award for Distinguished Service (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Property - Woodstock Inn (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Property - Woodstock Inn - A - Z (Box 88, Folder 5-6)
  - Property - Woodstock Inn - Guest List, Egg Nog Party, 1993 January 1 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Property - Woodstock Inn - Dr. Cook's Garden, 1992-1996 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Property - Woodstock Inn - Democratic Governor's Association, 1992-1996 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1992-1996 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1985-1995 (Box 89, Folder 1-4)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Budget and Financials, 1991-1995 (Box 89, Folder 5-15)
  - LSR - Chase Securities (Box 90, Folder 1-5)
    Restricted - Financial material.
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Securities (Box 90, Folder 6-10)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1992-1996 (Box 91, Folder 1-7)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - Property - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Personnel and Compensation (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Property - Wyoming, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Property - Wyoming - A - Z (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Appraisals, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Employees, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Firestone Purchase, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Landscaping, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Planning, 1979-1987 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits - General, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits - Appreciation, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 13-14)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Visits, 1995 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Property - Wyoming - Valley Ranch - Wirth Design Associates, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Quotations, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Remarks, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Remarks - Presentation to Lady Bird Johnson, the First LSR Conservation Award, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Robinson, James D. III and Linda, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Robinson, Joseph, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Rockefeller, David and Margaret, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Rockefeller, David Jr. and Diana, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Rockefeller, Blanchette, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Rockefeller, Steven C., 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Rodriquez, Chi Chi, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Ross, Steven J. and Courtney, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Rudin, Lewis, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - See, Alva B. Jr., 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Sherill, H. Virgil and Betty, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Sinatra, Francis and Barbara, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Sixtieth Wedding Anniversary, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Fred (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Soldwedel, Mrs. Frederic, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Stevenson, Dr. George C., 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Strong, Mrs. Maurice - Loan, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 12-13)
  - Telephones, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Princeton Thesis, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Trips - A - Z (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Trips - California-Hawaii (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Trips - Carribean, 1992-1996 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Trips - Europe (France and Ireland), 1993-1994 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Trips - Indonesia, 1993 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - Trips - London, 1994 October (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Trips - Mexico, 1989-1996 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Trusts, 1992-1995 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Trusts - Descendents of LSR Trust 5012, 1992-1995 (Box 94, Folder 6-9)
  - Trusts - Charitable Lead Trust 5315 - Marion R. Weber, 1992-1994 (Box 94, Folder 10-12)
  - Trusts - Charitable Lead Trust 5515 - Descendents of L. Waletzky, 1992-1994 (Box 94, Folder 13-15)
  - Trusts - Charitable Lead Trust 5705 - Larry Rockefeller, 1992-1994 (Box 94, Folder 16-18)
  - Van Der Kemp, Gerald and Florence, 1992-1996 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Waletzky, Naomi, 1992-1996 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Waletzky, Naomi - The Society of Mayflower Descendents Debutantes Ball, 1993 November 5 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Whyte, William Holly, Jr. and Jenny Bell, 1992-1996 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Works of Art - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 94, Folder 23-24)
  - Works of Art - Armstrong, James B., 1992-1996 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Works of Art - Ellen R. C. Pomeroy Dat-So-La-Le (Indian Baskets), 1993-1994 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Works of Art - Kagan, Rod, 1992-1996 (Box 95, Folder 2)
- Mary French Rockefeller - Charitable Gifts, 1992-1996; 37
  - Rockefeller, Mary French - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Mary French - Charitable Gift Letters - A - Y, 1996 (Box 95, Folder 4-25)
  - Rockefeller, Mary French - Awards, 1992-1996 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Rockefeller, Mary French - Dinners-Luncheons, 1992-1996 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - African Medical and Research Foundation, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Appalachian Ministries Educational Resource Center (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Appeal of Conscience Foundation (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - The Brick Presbyterian Church, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Central Park Conservancy, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Chamber Music Society of Lincoln Center, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Choate Rosemary Hall Foundation, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - The Winston Churchill Foundation of the USA, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Bruce and Cindy Halsted - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Christian Solidarity International, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Family Care International, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - Fellowship of Christians in Universities and Schools, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Leighton Ford Ministries, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Freedom from Hunger, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Fresh Air Fund, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - Girls, Incorporated, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 19)
  - Interfaith Neighbors, Inc., 1997 (Box 104, Folder 20)
  - The Hudson Valley Writers Center, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 21)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood House, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 22)
  - The Lighthouse, Inc., 1997 (Box 104, Folder 23)
  - Madison Square Boys and Girls Club, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 24)
  - Manhattan Country Club, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 25)
  - New York Philharmonic, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 26)
  - Planned Parenthood of New York City, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 27)
  - The Salvation Army of Greater New York, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 28)
  - Save the Children, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 29)
  - Shelburne Museum, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 30)
  - The Student Conservation Association, Inc., 1997 (Box 104, Folder 31)
  - The Thursday Club, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 32)
  - The Tevor Day School, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 33)
  - Trickle Up Program, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 34)
  - United States Committee for UNICEF, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 35)
  - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 36)
  - Channel 13 - WNET, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 37)
  - USO of Metropolitan New York, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 38)
  - Vassar College, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 39)
  - The Vermont Folk Life Center, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 40)
  - Vermont Studio Center, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 41)
  - The Whitney Museum of American Art, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 42)
  - WLIW Public Television, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 43)
  - Women's Bible Society of New York, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 44)
  - Women's Campaign Fund, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 45)
  - YWCA - World Service Council, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 46)
  - YWCA - White Plains and Central Westchester, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 47)
  - YWCA of the City of New York, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 48)
  - Women's City Club of New York, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 49)
  - Vassar Bequest, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1998 and 1997 Giving Schedule (Box 104, Folder 51)
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1992-1996; 38
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. - Estate, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Winthrop Paul Rockefeller, 1992-1996; 39
  - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1992-1996; 40
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1992-1996 (Box 96, Folder 6-7)
  - Meetings, 1996 June 4 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1996 December 12 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1996 October 4 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1996 March 7 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1995 December 14 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1995 October 6 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1995 June 6 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1995 March 9 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1994 December 15 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1994 October 13 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, 1994 June 16 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1994 March 8 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1993 December 16 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1993 October 19 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1993 June 17 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1993 March 9 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1992 December 17 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1992 October 6 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1992 June 17 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1992 April 7 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Pocantico Conference Center, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 11)
- Rockefeller and Company, 1993-1994; 41
  - Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc - Finances, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 12)
- Rockefeller Family Fund, 1992-1996; 42
  - Rockefeller Family Fund - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Rockefeller Family Office, 1992-1996; 43
  - Rockefeller Family Office - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Philanthropy, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Rockefeller and Company - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 97, Folder 16-17)
- Rockefeller Financial Services, 1992-1996; 44
  - Rockefeller Financial Services - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Financial Services - Pomeroy, 1991-1993 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Chairmanship, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Expenses, 1987-1992 (Box 98, Folder 4-8)
  - General, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Meetings, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Personnel - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Venrock, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Venrock - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Trust Company, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1992-1996; 45
  - Rockefeller Foundation - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 15)
- Rockefeller University, 1992-1996; 46
  - Rockefeller University - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 17)
- S - General, 1992-1996; 47
  - S - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 18)
- Science, 1992-1996; 48
  - Science - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 98, Folder 19-20)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Institute, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Center for Functional Research, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Center for Psychology and Social Change, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 4-5)
  - Center for Science in the Public Interest, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Foundation for Ethnobiology, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Science - General Files, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Frontier Science, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Noetic Sciences, 1992-1996 (Box 99, Folder 10-12)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - New York Hall of Science, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - New York Hall of Science - 2017:FA1325:021 - CNN News, "Microbes Museum: New York Hall of Science" video, VHS, 3 minutes (Box 2017:FA1325:021)
  - Orgone Biophysical Research Laboratory, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Society of Scientific Exploration, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - The Teller Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - UFO, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - UFO - General, 1993-1995 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - UFO - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - UFO - John Mack, 1992-1995 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - New Paradigm Symposium, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- T - General, 1992-1996; 49
  - T - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- W - General, 1992-1996; 50
  - W - Miscellaneous, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Westchester Organizations - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Winrock International, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 3-4)
  - Women - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Women - Ms. Foundation for Women, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Welfare, 1992-1996; 51
  - Welfare - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 13-14)
  - American Red Cross - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Citymeals-On-Wheels, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - United Service Organization (USO) - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Animals - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Blind - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Blind - The Lighthouse, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Blind - Seeing Eye, Inc., 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Community Centers - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Crime Prevention - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Day Nurseries - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Family Counseling - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Family Counseling - Family Institute of Cambridge, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 7-8)
  - Handicapped - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Handicapped - Dateable, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Handicapped - International Center for the Disabled (ICD), 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Homes - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Indians - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 13-14)
  - Indians - The Hopi Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Legal - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Musicians - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - United Funds - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Youth, 1992-1996; 52
  - Youth - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 7-9)
  - Boy Scouts of America - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Boy Scouts of America Greater New York Councils, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Boys Club of New York, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Boys and Girls Clubs of America, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Girl Scouts of America - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - One to One Partnership, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Police Athletic League, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Chi Chi Rodriquez Youth Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - YMCA - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - YMCA - Greater New York, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - New York City Division, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - YWCA of the USA, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 4-5)
  - YWCA of the USA - Fundraising, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Youth Camps - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Youth Camps - Camp Rising Sun-Clinton, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Homes - A - Z, 1992-1996 (Box 103, Folder 9)